Guide to the Edwin H. Armstrong papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Clippings, 1912-1954
  - FCC Hearing--FM and Television, Status of Radio, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Social Notes, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Doubting Comments and Hostile Comments, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - General, 1940 January-March, (5 Folders) (Box 22, Folder 22-26)
  - General, 1940 March-1941 February, (17 Folders) (Box 23, Folder 1-17)
  - Hostile and Doubting Comments, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Carter's "Static is Good Enough For Us," 1941 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - General, 1941 March-December, (12 Folders) (Box 24, Folder 3-14)
  - Dubious Comments, 1942 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - General, 1942 January-March, 1943, (8 Folders) (Box 24, Folder 16-23)
  - General, 1944 January-May (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Dubious Comments, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - General, 1944 May-1945 December, (13 Folders) (Box 25, Folder 3-15)
  - FCC Hearing and Controversy Regarding High and Low Bands, 1945-1946 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - General, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - FCC Frequency Allocation Decision, Controversy, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - FM Delay, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Freedom of Speech, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Foreign, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Unique and General, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Petrillo and Union, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Programming, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Political, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Retailing, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Technical, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Television, 1946, (2 Folders) (Box 25, Folder 28-29)
  - Major Armstrong--Sketches and Speeches, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Other Personalities, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - General Information Articles, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - FCC Denny's Prediction, 1947 January (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Armstrong's Speech at Atlantic City--Accuses RCA of Retarding FM, 1947 September (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Petrillo and Union, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - FCC and Senate Interstate Commerce Committee, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Delaying FM, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Freedom of Speech, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Hearing on Allocation of 44-50 Mc Band, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Retailing and Production, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Expansion and Predictions, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Promotion, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - FM Stations, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Relaying and FM Networks, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Advertisements, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Television, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Programming, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Broadcasting Code, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - FM Association, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - National Association of Broadcasters, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Other Organizations, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Technical Developments, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Equipment, Description of, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Educational FM, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Other FM Uses, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Foreign Clippings, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Progess, Delay and Reports on FM, 1947-1948 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Armstrong, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - FM Patent Suit--Armstrong vs. RCA, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - AFM--Petrillo
    - General, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - With FM, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - With Television, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Hearing by House Labor Committee Investigating Charge that AFM Holds Monopoly, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - "Petrillo's No Caesar in Wilds"--AP Story, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Congressional Activities, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Hearing of Lemke Bill Before House Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Senate Investigations into RCA Activities, 1948 May (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - FCC--General, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Allocations, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Members, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - FM
    - Broadcasting--Relaying and FM Networks, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Business--General, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 43)
      - Advertisments, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 44)
      - Future Progress and Predictions, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 45)
      - Radio Sets, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 46)
      - Promotion, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 47)
      - FM Equipment, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Organizations--General (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - FMA, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - IRE, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - NAB, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - RCA, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Personalities, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Technical Developments, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - Television--General, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 56)
    - Advertisements, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 57)
    - General, 1948-1949 (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - FCC
    - Hearing on Mayflower Ruling, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Hearing on 44-50 Band, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Foreign--General, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Australia and New Zealand, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Canada, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Continental Europe 1948 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Great Britain, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - South Africa, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - FM--General, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Broadcasting
      - Educational, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Future, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Programming, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Radio Stations, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Armstrong, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Low Band FM--W2XMN, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Congressional Activities--Senate Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - FCC--General, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Pertaining to FM, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Pertaining to Television, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Frequency Allocations, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Members, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Foreign--General, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Australia and New Zealand, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Canada, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Continental Europe, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - England and the British Isles, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - South Africa and Africa, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - FM--General, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Comments, Criticism, Letters to Editors, Hostile Propaganda, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Broadcasting--General, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 30)
      - Commercial, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 31)
      - Educational, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 32)
      - Experimental, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 33)
      - Programming, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 34)
      - Relaying and Networks, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Business--General, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 36)
      - Future--Progress, Predictions, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 37)
      - Promotion of, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 38)
      - Zenith Promotion of FM Sets, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Organizations--General, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - FMA, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - IRE, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - NAB, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Personalities, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Radio--General, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - General, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Technical Developments, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Television--General, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - Future, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 49)
    - Stations, Programming, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 50)
    - Technical Improvements, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - RCA, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - General, 1950, (2 Folders) (Box 28, Folder 21-22)
  - Armstrong, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Congressional Activities
    - House of Representatives, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 54)
    - Senate, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - FCC--General, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 56)
    - Pertaining to FM, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 57)
    - Pertaining to Television, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 58)
    - Frequency Allocations, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 59)
    - Members, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 60)
    - Engineering and Technical Data, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 61)
  - Foreign
    - Australia and New Zealand, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 62)
    - Canada, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 63)
    - Continental Europe, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 64)
    - England and British Isles, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 65)
    - South Africa and Africa, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 66)
  - Featured Articles and Odd Bits, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 67)
  - FM--General, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Controversial Opinions, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 68)
    - Broadcasting, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 69)
      - Commercial, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 70)
      - Educational, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 71)
      - Experimental, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 72)
      - Programming, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 73)
      - Relaying and Networks, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 74)
    - Business, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 75)
      - Future, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 76)
      - Promotion of, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 77)
    - Equipment, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 78)
    - Facsimile and Multiplexing, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 79)
    - Mobile and Emergency Uses, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 80)
    - Technical and Scientific Developments, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 81)
  - General, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 82)
  - Organizations--General, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 83)
  - Organizations--General, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - FMA, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 84)
    - IRE, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 85)
    - NAB, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 86)
    - Radio Club of America, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 87)
  - Personalities, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Radiation, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - RCA, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Radio Industry, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Television--General, 1950, (2 Folders) (Box 28, Folder 12-13)
    - Future, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Promotion, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Color, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Technical Developments and Improvements, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Stations, Networks and Improvements, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - RCA's, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Zenith's Phonevision, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - General, 1951, (5 Folders) (Box 29, Folder 3-7)
  - AFM--Petrillo, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Armstrong--General, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Congressional Activities--General, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - House, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Senate, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - FCC--General, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Pertaining to FM, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Pertaining to Television, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Frequency Allocation, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Members, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Pertaining to Facsimile and Multiplexing, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Foreign--General, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Australia and New Zealand, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Canada, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Continental Europe, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - England and the British Isles, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Africa, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Technical, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - FM
    - Odd Bits and Feature Articles, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Controversial Opinions, Comments, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - Broadcasting--General, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 43)
      - Commercial, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 44)
      - Educational, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 45)
      - Experimental, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 46)
      - Programming, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 47)
      - Relaying and Networks, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - Business--General, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Production, Future, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Promotion of, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Equipment--Other than Radio Sets, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Facsimile and Multiplexing, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Mobile, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 49)
    - Mobile and Energy Uses, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Technical and Scientific Developments, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Organizations
    - FMA, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - NARTB, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - RTMA, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Personalities, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Radio Industry and AM Networks, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Television--General, 1951, (2 Folders) (Box 29, Folder 13-14)
    - Future, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Promotion, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Color, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Technical Improvements, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Stations, Networks, Programming, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - RCA's, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Zenith's Phonevision, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Radiation, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - General, 1952, (2 Folders) (Box 29, Folder 23-24)
  - Domestic, 1952 January-December, (12 Folders) (Box 29, Folder 25-36)
  - General, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Television--General, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - FM Interference, European Comments Regarding FM, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Foreign--General, 1952-1953 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Domestic--General, 1953, (4 Folders) (Box 30, Folder 5-8)
  - General, 1953, (2 Folders) (Box 30, Folder 9-10)
  - Television, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Armstrong's Death, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Domestic, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Foreign, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Television, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Series IV: Alphabetical Files, 1886-1980
  This series is comprised of a large set of files which appears to have been Armstrong's filing system, which was expanded upon at a later date to include litigation, the Armstrong Memorial Research Foundation Files, and others. This series is organized alphabetically by both name and subject.
  Throughout the series there are folders which are filed by individual name. The majority are engineering publications, filed by author. Others contain legal statements, testimony, correspondence and memoranda.
  There are also large sets of litigation files, which contain material relating to specific cases, generally filed by defendant. These files contain testimony, transcripts, abstracts, notes, disclosures, technical reports and papers, license agreements, articles, press releases, correspondence, legal memoranda, instruction manuals, exhibits and patent file wrappers. Large amounts of Armstrong's and relevant others original work including correspondence, diagrams, notes, testing data, photographs, notebooks, logbooks, and patent disclosures used in exhibits can be found under litigation files as well. The following organizations can be found amongst litigation; Admiral Corp., American Telephone & Telegraph, Co., Arvin Industries, Avco Corp., Bendix Radio and Aviation Corp,. De Forest Radio and Telegraph Co., DuMont Laboratories, Emerson Radio, FADA Radio and Electric Co., Gilfillan Bros., Hoffman Radio Corp., Fred M. Link, Motorola, Inc., Packard-Bell Co., Philco Corp., Radio and Television, Inc., Radio Corp. of America and the National Broadcasting Corp., the Radio Craftsman, Inc., Sentinel Radio, Sylvania Electric Products, Inc. and Wells-Gardner and Co. The litigation files found within this series should be researched in conjunction with series five as the two overlap.
  - Adair, George P.--Biographical Sketch, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Adams, E., William Hubbard and A.M. Syeles--"A New Permanent From Powdered Magnanese Bismuthide," 1952 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Admiral Corporation Litigation
    - Armstrong vs. Admiral Corp.--Pleadings, Extra Copies, Papers Not Used, 1948-1958, (2 Folders) (Box 33, Folder 3-4)
  - Allen, Edward Jr--Publications and FCC Testimony, 1946-1947 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - "Very High Frequency and Ultra High Frequency Signal Ranges As Limited by Noise and Co-channel Interference," 1947 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - IRE Paper and Discussion Apertaining Thereto, 1945-1947, (2 Folders) (Box 33, Folder 7-8)
  - Aircraft--Writings Regarding, 1939 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Allsop, Ray--Correspondence, 1946-1952 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Alpine, New Jersey
    - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Programs, 1941-1948, (2 Folders) (Box 33, Folder 12-13)
    - Radio Station, General--CBS and NBC--Includes Lenox R. Lohr, 1939-1941 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence Regarding Closing of FM Station KE2XCC, 1954, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Listener Letters, 1953-1954 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Power Supply, 1947-1954 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - W2XMN--Program Schedules, 1940-1941, undated (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Transcriptions and Pick-Ups--Associated Program Service, Inc., 1940-1949 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Los Angeles and Newark Radio--Geodite Survey, New York--Diagrams and Notes, Includes Negative of Equipment, undated (Negative) (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Personnel--Resumes, 1942-1953 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Bell Laboratories Record volume XXXI, no. 1--Includes Diagrams, 1953, undated (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Instruction Sheets, 1938-1940 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Data, 1945-1948 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Transmitter, 100Mc FM, GE Z 9C24 Tubes, 1938-1945 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Motors and Generators, 1942, undated (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - 880 P.A., 1940 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - 889 P.A., 1940 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - 110Mc Transmitter, 1939 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Programs--KE2XCC, 1941-1952 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Wiring and Power Control Circuit Data, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Radio Engineering Laboratories, Inc.--Wiring Diagram for 5B Panel, 1940 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Blueprint--Plan of Plot--Radio Station W2XMN, Alpine, New Jersey, 1938 January 18 (Box 224, Folder 5)
    - 33 1/3 LP
      - "Final Sign-off Program of Major E.H. Armstrong's Pioneer FM Radio Radio Station--KE2XCC," 1954 March 6 (Box 224, Folder 6)
    - 93.1 Mc Recycling Circuit, Includes 93.1 Mc Quad Obsolete Diagrams, 1948-1949 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Regarding Alpine, 1939-1953 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Report on Troubles Occuring on Radio Program Line No. 251 Between Muzak Studios, NYC, and W2XMN-W2XEA, Alpine, NJ, 1939-1948 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Alpine Log Sheets, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - FCC Authorization for Radio Station W2XMN, 1936-1958 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Number of Transmitter Offs During the Period 1942 Jan 1-December 31--Includes Description of Equipment Used in Propagation Tests, 1942, 1947, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Commercial Radio Equipment Co.--Engineering Appendix I, An Engineering Amendment to Application--File No. BPH-513, WFMN, Alpine, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Air Raid Alarm and Precautions--Project Conelrad, 1951-1954 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Programs--Multiplex Tests--FM Stations Heard at KE2XCC--Correspondence, 1938-1953 (Photographs) (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Construction and Operation of W2XMN--Correspondence, 1937-1938 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Concentric Line--Drawings and Invoices, 1939-1949 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Telco Lines, Trouble With--Logs and Correspondence, 1941-1948 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Liscenses From FCC, 1943-1952, (2 Folders) (Box 34, Folder 13-14)
    - Rectifiers, Drawings and Correspondence, 1940 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Property--14+ Acres, Phelps Parcel, Correspondence, 1937-1958 (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - W2XNM Site, Correspondence, 1937-1952 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Tubes--Drawings, Blueprints, Correspondence, 1944 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Orders, 1943-1953 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Blueprints, Spray-pump, Rectifier Assembly From Various Elevations, Transmitter Schematics, 1936-1937 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Sketches of Items Being Made, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Wiring Diagram, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - 50 Kw FM RF Schematic, Blueprints (Photographs), undated (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Original Modulation Drawings, undated (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Rhombic Antenna, AFIXHR, Drawings, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Water Cooler--Instructions and Drawings, 1942 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Diagrams and Instructions--Tubes, 1951-1952 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Modulators--Modulator Unit Normal Meter Readings, 1940-1941 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Monitor Receiver--Circuit Diagram and Parts List, 1941, undated (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Drawings, Blueprints, Sketches and Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - General Electric--Panel Schematic for W2XMN, 1940-1941 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Received Orders, Invoices and Drawings, 1952-1954 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Westinghouse Electric--Correspondence, Diagrams and Data, 1946, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Facsimile Testing--Includes Drawings by John W. Bose, 1940 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Meter Readings
      - W2XMN--Frequency 42.8Mc, 1944-1946 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - KE2XCC--Frequency 93.1Mc, 1951-1953 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - W2XEA--Frequency 93.1Mc, 1947-1951 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - W2MXN--Frequency 44.1Mc, 1947-1949 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Rhombic Antenna--Drawings, 1939-11953 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - General Electric--FM Circular Antenna Characteristics, Correspondence and Drawings, 1942-1950 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Antenna--Donut--92.1Mc, Drawings, 1946-1947 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Tower Lighting--Drawings, Blueprints and Correspondence, 1937-1954 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - New Antenna--Concentric Line Feed, 43.1Mc, 1941-1942 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Facsimile Transmissions--Columbia Lboratory to KEA46 to KE2XCC, 1949 (Box 36)
    - Logbooks
      - Number 1--W2XMN, 117.43 Mc, 111 Mc, 92.5 Mc--WFMN, 104.9 Mc, 1939 April 3-1949 July 20 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - W2XMN, 42.8 Mc
        - Number 2, 1939 August 14-1940 January 31 (Box 37, Folder 2)
        - Number 3, 1940 February 1-April 21 (Box 37, Folder 3)
        - Number 4, 1940 April 22-August 31 (Box 37, Folder 4)
        - Number 5, 1940 September 1-December 31 (Box 37, Folder 5)
        - Number 6, 1941 January 1-May 21 (Box 37, Folder 6)
        - Number 7, 1941 May 22-October 14 (Box 38, Folder 1)
        - Number 8, 1941 October 15-1942 March 8 (Box 38, Folder 2)
        - Number 9, 1942 March 9-August 7 (Box 38, Folder 3)
        - Number 10, 1942 August 8-1943 January 6 (Box 38, Folder 4)
        - Number 11, 1943 January 7-June 7 (Box 38, Folder 5)
        - Number 12, 1943 June 8-November 6 (Box 38, Folder 6)
        - Number 13, 1943 November 7-1944 April 6 (Box 39, Folder 1)
        - Number 14, 1944 April 7-September 6 (Box 39, Folder 2)
        - Number 15, 1944 Sptember 7-1945 February 5 (Box 39, Folder 3)
        - Number 16, 1945 February 6-July 7 (Box 39, Folder 4)
        - Number 17, 1945 July 8-December 6 (Box 39, Folder 5)
        - Number 18, 1945 December 7-1946 May 6 (Box 39, Folder 6)
        - Number 19, 1946 May 7-October 5 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - W2XEA, 92.1 Mc
        - Number 1, 1946 February 8-July 29 (Box 40, Folder 2)
        - Number 2, 1946 July 30-December 28 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - WFMN, 98.9 Mc
        - 1945 November 30-1946 February 7, May 24 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - W2XMN, 42.8, 44.1 Mc
        - Number 20, 1946 October 6-1947 March 6 (at 44.1 Mc beginning January 24, 1947) (Box 40, Folder 5)
        - Number 21, 1947 March 7-August 5 (Box 40, Folder 6)
        - Number 22, 1947 August 6-1948 January 4 (Box 41, Folder 1)
        - Number 23, 1948 January 5-June 2 (Box 41, Folder 2)
        - Number 24, 1948 June 3-October 28 (Box 41, Folder 3)
        - Number 25, 1948 October 29-1949 March 27 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - W2XEA, 92.1 Mc
        - Number 3, 1946 December 29-1947 May 29 (Box 41, Folder 5)
        - Number 4, 1947 May 30-1947 October 28 (Box 42, Folder 1)
        - Number 5, 1947 October 29-1948 March 28 (Box 42, Folder 2)
        - Number 6, 1948 March 29- August 23 (Box 42, Folder 3)
        - Number 7, 1948 August 24-1949 January 19 (at 93.1 Mc beginning December 9, 1948) (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - W2XEA, 93.1 Mc (up until 1949 April 27) and KE2XCC, 93.1 Mc (beginning 1949 April 28)
        - Number 8, 1949 January 20-June 19 (Box 42, Folder 5)
        - Number 9, 1949 June 20-November 16 (Box 42, Folder 6)
        - Number 10, 1949 November 17-1950 April 17 (Box 43, Folder 1)
        - Number 11, 19 50 April 18-September 16 (Box 43, Folder 2)
        - Number 12, 1950 September 17-1951 February 16 (Box 43, Folder 3)
        - Number 13, 1951 February 17-1951 July 17 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - W2XMN, 44.1 Mc